I was sent by Leah's father from Adamawa State.
This girl was abducted alongside other school girls at Dapchi since 2018.
Why is the father not here?
The father is not well; he is traumatised.
I am his elder brother.
We want you to pray for us; we have gone to many places to look for help but could not get it.
We heard about you, that is why we came for your assistance and help.
I am Yakubu Nkeki, Chairman Of Abducted Chibok Girls' Parents, from Borno State.
Please, sir, help us!
The pictures of the girls I'm holding with me - they are 112 Chibok girls that are yet to be released
in the hands of the captors.
We have gone to so many places seeking for solution but there was no answer.
We heard from many people that there is a Prophet, T.B. Joshua, in Lagos
that is delivering people all over the nation.
That is why we from Chibok, on behalf of the 112 parents,
whose daughters have not yet been released came to seek for solution.
Help us to pray so that the 112 girls in the hands of the captors might be released.
We believe God will intervene and bring them home safely.
Stand up and you have to promise:
This coming week - Tuesday, Wednesday, Friday -
you must promise, you have to be in an attitude of prayer.
With all your heart, pray and fast -
Tuesday, Wednesday, Friday - everyone.
Viewers all over the world, Tuesday, Wednesday, Friday,
be in attitude of prayer and fasting.
With all your heart, pray for these children.
Pray for the other children and Leah as well.
Your prayer - for release!
I'm carrying all of you and the viewers all over the world along.
I will lead you.
Tuesday, Wednesday, Friday.
After you have done that, I know...
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Are you ready?
[Yes!]
Let me see your heart and your hand!
Viewers all over the world - join us Tuesday, Wednesday, Friday.
This is special for you on Tuesday, Wednesday, Friday for their release!
Lift up your voice.
Oh Lord, whatever sin they might have committed,
their families, wherever, whatever - Your mercy!
Have mercy on us!
We ask for Your mercy - mercy of release!
In Jesus Christ's name!
This is commission.
The Lord has commissioned you for this job -
Tuesday, Wednesday, Friday.
This is where you will know that God loves you just like any of His Apostles.
Thank you for your promise.
You may be seated. Thank you.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
STANDARD FOR LIFE
Sir, you are welcome, in Jesus' name.
Can you please introduce yourself and those who are standing with you.
My name is Yakubu Nkeki.
I'm the Chairman of Abducted Chibok Girls' Parents
that were abducted April 14, 2014 in Chibok local government, Borno State.
Here standing at my right hand side are the parents of the Chibok girls
that have not yet been released - 112 girls.
These are some of the parents.
Some are still at home.
We came here because we have visited many different places,
looking for solution to rescue the remaining girls.
Initially, they were 276 girls abducted.
In the process of negotiation, the government were able to rescue 113 girls.
We know that the government has tried its best.
Soldiers have tried their best.
Many soldiers have lost their lives in the process of rescuing these poor girls
from the hands of their captors.
We the Chibok girls' parents, appreciate the effort of the government
but there still remain 112 girls.
Since 2016, we have not received any credible information about them.
We have been looking for solution;
I, personally, have been to different countries: Germany, South Africa and many others.
We heard that there is a prophet in Lagos called Prophet T.B. Joshua
who delivers people from the hands of captors, from prison and delivers people from demons.
And those who are even crippled, walk!
This is what made us come to represent the parents of the 112 girls from Chibok
and to pray over these poor girls.
We know, with the power and miracles we have been seeing, God will bring the solution
through Prophet T.B. Joshua and God will release them, definitely.
By Sunday April 14, 2019 these poor girls will be exactly five years in the hands of their captors.
We do not know the condition they are in now.
Due to the pain of losing these poor girls, 34 parents also died
as they refused to eat or drink.
They were traumatised.
We believe definitely that the problem of these poor girls will be over
since we are here in The SCOAN.
He even ordered the nations to join him in praying for the release of the remaining 112 Chibok girls.
We believe, definitely they will be released.
He said that people around the world should fast on Tuesday, Wednesday and Friday.
By this, we know that God will intervene.
My name is Yana Galang.
I come from Chibok in Borno State, Nigeria.
The picture of the girl in my hand now is of my own biological daughter,
by name Rifkatu Galang.
She is one of the Chibok girls that was abducted on the 14th April 2014 by terrorists.
She is still with them and I don't know where she is
and I don't know what her condition is -
maybe she eats or drinks, I don't know.
But I know and believe that as we have come here to The SCOAN,
we believe in God, that God will intervene in this issue,
that these our children will be released very soon by the grace of God.
We believe, the faith that has brought them, will see them through
and these children will come out and they will give a testimony, in Jesus' name.
The anointed man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua, has sent us to you
that you have come all the way long from Borno State in the Northern part of Nigeria
and the man of God knows all the expenses that you must have had
in order to come here today as a group
and also your accommodation, feeding - the man of God is so much concerned
and moved by the Spirit of God.
He said, we should give you the sum of 452,000 Naira.
This is the sum of 452,000 Naira for all of you
to cover your transport expenses, feeding, accommodation.
Also 'The Mirror' book for the salvation of your soul.
Abducted Chibok Girls' Parents Receive 452,000
Naira From T.B. Joshua & Emmanuel TV Partners
Thank you very much. We appreciate it.
May God bless him in abundance.
We never expected that we would even get close to him
but he even opened up, shaked hands with us and listened to our problem.
Thank you very much. We appreciate it.
And it is just a beginning and it shows that really, our daughters will be back soon.
Thank you very much.
I'm Yunana Sharibu.
I'm the senior brother to Nathaniel Sharibu, the father of Leah.
The picture in our hand is a picture of Leah Sharibu and her mother.
Her father cannot be around because he is not well.
The same applies to the mother.
Being the senior brother in the family, I decided to represent the family here.
The man beside me is an uncle to the family.
He is an evangelist residing in Yola.
Leah Sharibu has been in captivity since the 19th of April, 2018.
There were about 119 school girls at Dapchi
and all of them were returned after some time, with the exception of Leah.
We have travelled to many places in search for a solution, to get this girl back.
But all failed.
So now we heard about Emmanuel TV.
We came together with the parents of the Chibok abducted girls.
So Leah has been now one year and two months in captivity.
I will even start to say my testimony
because what I have seen today is more or less a testimony to me.
The man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua, has sent us to present to the family
the total cash sum of 700,000 Naira.
That is the total sum of 700,000 Naira by the anointed man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua,
and the Emmanuel TV Partners, and this money is to support the parents.
Out of this money, the man of God has instructed
that 500,000 Naira cash should be given to the mother and father of Leah
because of the condition they are in now.
200,000 Naira for you to take care of your feeding, transportation and accommodation.
And also 'The Mirror' book for the salvation of your soul.
He has also sent spiritual items.
We are very grateful.
We want to extend our regards and gratitude to the man of God.
We are very grateful. Thank you very much.
TT: Mel Flowers 18/04/2019